Guide to the Donald Clifford Gallup Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2000 Acquisition, 1918-1964; 10; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  - T. S. Eliot Papers
    - Correspondence
      - Letters to Brigit Patmore
        - 231. Autograph letter, signed: London, "Wednesday". Four pages, 18cm., 1919 May 14?
          Signed "Tom". On a misunderstanding at dinner the night before. Letters, 292.
        - 232. Autograph letter, signed: London, "Friday". Two pages, 18cm., 1919 May 16?
          Signed "Tom". With autograph letter, signed, from Vivien Eliot, "Thursday", and one dated "Sunday night." Letters, 293.
        - 233. Autograph letter, signed: London, "Tuesday". Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1919 May 27
          Signed with initials. On understanding people. Letters, 293-94.
        - 234. Autograph letter, signed: London. Three pages, 26cm., 1919 April?
          Signed with initials. On understanding people.
        - 235. Autograph letter, signed: London. Two pages, 26 1/2cm., 1919 June 15
          Signed with initials. On his activities. Letters, 303.
        - 236. Autograph letter, signed: London. One page, 18cm., 1921 March 2
          Signed with initials. On meeting. Letters, 437.
        - 237. Autograph letter, signed: London. Two pages, 22 1/2cm., 1921 March 17
          Signed "Tom". On his wife's health. Letters, 441.
      - Letters to the Rev. and Mrs. John Carroll Perkins
        Purchased (1) single typed letter, signed, of 21 Aug 1954, with manuscript "A Valedictory" and inscribed copy of Old Possum's Book to Mary M. Quillan, Seven Gables Bookshop, 1961; (2) rest, with corrected typescript "A Valedictory" and another poem, Goodspeed's, 1972.
        - 238. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 18cm., 1931 September 3
        - 239. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1932 August 29
        - 240. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 23cm., 1932 October 12
        - 241. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 14cm., 1932 November 14
        - 242. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 14cm., 1933 May 15
        - 243. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 14cm., 1933 May 18
        - 244. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 14cm., 1933 May 25
        - 245. Typed letter, signed: Randolph, N.H. One page, 28cm., 1933 June 12
        - 246. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1934 May 15
        - 247. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1934 May 17
        - 248. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1934 May 29
        - 249. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1934 June 1
        - 250. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 18 1/2cm., 1934 June 5
        - 251. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1934 June 18
        - 252. Autograph letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1934 July 30
          With typed postscript.
        - 253. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 18cm., 1934 August 1
        - 254. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1934 September 4
        - 255. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1934 September 24
        - 256. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1934 October 22
        - 257. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1934 October 30
        - 258. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1935 February 8
        - 259. Easter card, with ALS. One page, 10cm., 1935
        - 260. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1935 May 15
        - 261. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 18 1/2cm., 1935 May 20
        - 262. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1935 May 5
        - 263. Autograph letter, signed: London. Two pages, 18 1/2-24cm., 1935 July 17
        - 264. Autograph letter, signed: Ciliau Aeron. Three pages, 18cm., 1935 August 1
        - 265. Autograph letter, signed: Ciliau Aeron. Two pages, 18cm., 1935 August 6
        - 266. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 18cm., 1935 August 15
        - 267. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1935 August 28
        - 268. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 18-23cm., 1935 September 10
        - 269. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1935 September 30
        - 270. Typed letter, signed: London. One pages, 25 1/2cm., 1935 October 11
        - 271. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1935 December 11
        - 272. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1936 January 7
        - 273. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1936 July 10
        - 274. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1936 September 30
        - 275. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1936 August 19
        - 276. Autograph letter, signed: on board "Alaunia". Three pages, 19 1/2cm., 1936 October 2
        - 277. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 January 21
        - 278. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 April 30
        - 279. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 May 4
        - 280. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 May 7
        - 281. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 May 27
        - 282. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1937 June 7
        - 283. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1937 June 16
        - 284. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 August 16
        - 285. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 September 3
        - 286. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 September 9
        - 287. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 October 19
        - 288. Typed letter, signed: London, All Souls. One page, 18 1/2cm., 1937
        - 289. Autograph letter, signed: London, "Wednesday". One page, 25 1/2cm., 1937 November
        - 290. Autograph letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 January 7
        - 291. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 March 29
        - 292. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 June 18
          Signed "Tom". With manuscript postscript.
        - 293. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 June 29
        - 294. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 August 24
          Signed "T. Possum". In imitation of the style of Henry James.
        - 295. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1938 September 11
        - 296. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1938 September 27
        - 297. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages 18 1/2-23cm., 1938 October 2
        - 298. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 October 17
        - 299. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1938 November 2
        - 300. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1939 January 27
        - 301. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1939 June 6
        - 302. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1939 June 17
        - 303. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1939 July 26
        - 304. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1940 June 27
        - 305. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1941 September 20
        - 306. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1942 September 3
        - 307. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 21cm., 1944 January 3
        - 308. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 21cm., 1944 December 26
          Signature clipped.
        - 309. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 21cm., 1945 March 5
        - 310. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 21cm., 1945 July 23
        - 311. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 21cm, 1946 March 26
        - 312. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 28cm., 1946 August 14
        - 313. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 21cm., 1946 September 16
        - 314. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 18 1/2cm., 1947 February 22
        - 315. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass.. One page, 28cm., 1947 June 12
        - 316. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 21cm., 1947 August 14
        - 317. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 21cm., 1947 September 25
        - 318. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 20 1/2cm., 1947 December 6
        - 319. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1948 June 3
        - 320. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 20 1/2cm., 1948 July 11
        - 321. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1948 September 4
        - 322. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1948 September 18
        - 323. Autograph letter, signed: New York, "Saturday". Two pages, 18 1/2cm., 1948 October 2
        - 324. Typed letter, signed: Princeton, N. J. One page, 16 12 1/2cm., 1948 October 12
        - 325. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1949 February 22
        - 326. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 20 1/2cm., 1949 July 2
        - 327. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1949 October 26
        - 328. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 20 1/2cm., 1949 December 31
        - 329. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1950 April 17
        - 330. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1950 June 12
        - 331. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1950 June 18
        - 332. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1950 July 9
        - 333. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 24 1/2cm., 1950 August 8
        - 334. Typed letter, signed: [London?]. One page, 24 1/2cm., 1950 September 19
        - 335. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1950 December 31
        - 336. Typed letter, signed: [London?]. One page, 24 1/2cm., 1951 April 4
        - 337. Typed letter, signed: [London?]. One page, 24 1/2cm., 1951 May 17
        - 338. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 20 1/2cm., 1951 August 25
        - 339. Typed letter, signed: [London]. One page, 24 1/2cm., 1951 October 14
        - 340. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1952 January 8
        - 341. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1952 February 10
        - 342. Typed letter: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1952 August 4
        - 343. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1952 December 2
        - 344. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1953 March 15
        - 345. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1953 November 8
        - 346. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1954 June 4
        - 347. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 20 1/2cm., 1954 August 21
        - 348. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1955 January 17
        - 349. Autograph letter, signed: London. Two pages, 23cm., 1955 April 23
        - 350. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 22cm., 1955 May 8
        - 351. Autograph letter, signed: Washington, D. C. Two pages, 18cm., 1955 May 21
        - 352. Typed letter, signed: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 28cm., 1955 May 29
        - 353. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 25 1/2cm., 1955 October 18
        - 354. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1955 November 27
        - 355. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1956 November 11
      - 356. Typed letter, signed, to Paul Potts: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1948 June 8
        On reprinting an obituary notice and George Orwell. Purchased Bertram Rota Ltd., 1953.
      - 357. Typed letter, signed, to C. U. P. Robinson: London. One page, 21cm., 1948 June 21
        Advice on writing poetry. Purchased Bertram Rota Ltd., 1956.
      - Letters to John Rodker
        Purchased Gotham Book Mart, Inc. 1935.
        - 358. Autograph letter, signed: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1918 December 9
          On contributing to the Egoist. Letters, 260.
        - 359. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 27cm., 1920 January 20
          On Rodker's publishing schemes, and Ara Vus Prec.
      - Letters to Walter Hanks Shaw
        On contributing to the Criterion. Purchased House of Books Ltd., 1937.
        - 360. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 12/cm., 1924 December 22
        - 361. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1925 October 2
        - 362. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1926 November 3
        - 363. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 26 1/2cm., 1926 December 14
        - 364. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1927 February 28
          With manuscript postscript.
        - 365. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1927 May 3
        - 366. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1927 June 23
        - 367. Typed letter, signed: London. Two pages, 26 1/2cm., 1927 July 25
        - 368. Typed letter, signed: London. One page, 26 1/2cm., 1927 November 8
      - 369. Autograph letter, signed, to Clement K. Shorter: London. One page, 23cm., 1920 April 19
        On Ara Vus Prec. Purchased Stonehill, 1940? Letters, 379.
      - 370. Typed letter, signed, to John Singer: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1943 June 16
        Criticizing his poetry. Purchased Bertram Rota Ltd., 1954.
      - 370a. Typed letter, signed, to Charles Smyth: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1939 November 23
        Gift of Charles H. Wessels, 1989.
      - 371. Typed letter, signed, to Stephen Spender: London. One page, 20 1/2cm., 1952 January 23
        Enclosing Bad Ems manuscript. Purchased Stonehill.
      - 372. Typed letter, signed, to Chauncey B. Tinker: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 13 1/2cm., 1933 April 10
        Gift of Prof. Tinker, 1937. (See verso of original).
      - 373. Typed letter, signed, to Hugh Walpole: London. One page, 25 1/2cm., 1940 April 19
        Enclosing East Coker manuscript notes.
        Purchased Stonehill, 1940.
      - 374. Autograph draft telegram to Kurt Wolff: Cambridge, Mass. One page, 14 1/2cm., 1952 May 15
        On typed telegram from Wolff to Eliot, 15 May 1952.
        Purchased House of Books Ltd., 1952. (who bought it from Mrs. Henry Eliot, Jr.)
- June 2000 Acquisition, 1912-1962; 11; 0.42; (1 box)
  The June 2000 Aquistion consists of correspondence between Donald C. Gallup and Gertrude Stein as well as between Gallup and Alice B. Toklas. Other papers consist of uncorrected proofs of Gertrude Stein's What is Remembered and a copy of Camera Work, (August 1912) inscribed to Donald Gallup by Gertrude Stein and Alice B. Toklas, Paris, Oct 1945.
  Organized under two headings: Correspondence and Other Papers.
  - Correspondence
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1940-1946; 2 (Box 24)
    - Toklas, Alice B., 1946-1962; 12
    - Letter from Alice B. Toklas to David James, 1951 March 18
  - Other Papers
    - Toklas, Alice B. What is Remembered; uncorrected proofs, undated
    - Camera Work, Special Number, 1912
- July 2000 Acquisition, 1944-1999; 12; 1.21; (2 boxes)
  The July 2000 Acquisition contains diaries and notes in the hand of Carlotta Monterey O'Neill, letters to Donald C. Gallup relating to the diaries, as well as soundscriber recordings.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 26 (Soundscriber discs): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Carlotta Monterey O'Neill Papers
    - Diaries, 1944-1957; 9 (Box 25)
    - Notes, 1959, undated; 3
    - Correspondence with Donald Gallup, 1959-1999; 1; (1 Soundscriber disc)
    - Notes for Donald, 1959 May; 1; (14 Soundscriber discs)
  - Restricted Fragile Material
    Box 26, 113 - 115 (sound recordings and computer disk): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey. Tape made for DC Gallup", 1959 August; (1 Soundscriber disc) (Box 26)
    - "Carlotta Monterey O'Neill. Soundscriber Records", 1958-1959; (14 Soundscriber discs)
- July 2000 Acquisition, undated; 13; 2; (2 boxes)
  The July 2000 Acquisition contains photocopies of work notes and typescripts of Eugene O'Neill's eleven-play cycle A Tale of Possessors Self-Dispossessed from the Eugene O'Neill Papers.
  - O'Neill, Eugene. A Tale of Possessors Self-Dispossessed
    - "The Career of Bessie Bower", undated (Box 27)
    - "Robespierre", undated
    - "Runaway Slave Play", undated
    - "It Cannot Be Mad", undated; 2
    - "A Touch of the Poet", undated; 3
    - "More Stately Mansions", undated; 10
    - "The Calms of Capricorn", undated; 11 (Box 28)
    - "Cycle", undated; 8
    - "And Give Me Death", undated; 5
    - "The Earth Is the Limit", undated; 2
    - "Greed of the Meek", undated; 2
    - "Hair of the Dog", undated; 2
    - "The Man on Iron Horseback", undated; 2
    - "Nothing Is Lost Than Honor", undated; 2
    - Notes, undated
- April 2001 Acquisition, 1866-2000; 14; 78.5; (87 boxes) + 4 record album storage, 4 art, 1 object storage
  The April 2001 Acquisition consists of correspondence, research files, writings by Donald Gallup and others, notes, printed material, photographs, sound recordings, and artwork. Correspondence and Subject Files contain personal and professional correspondence, as well as personal and educational files of Donald Gallup. This groups also includes transcripts, photocopies, and photostats of T. S. Eliot, Ezra Pound, Gertrude Stein, and Thornton Wilder correspondence. Other papers consist of research files documenting Gallup's editorial work; transcripts, drafts, and galley proofs of writings by Donald Gallup, including What Mad Pursuits and Pigeons on the Granite; newspaper clippings and other printed ephemera about or relating to T. S. Eliot; the papers of Townsend Miller; and various publications by Gertrude Stein, Thornton Wilder, and Eugene O'Neill. Printed material consists of published articles by Donald C. Gallup, various exhibition catalogues and bookseller catalogues. Artwork includes a framed pen & wash drawing by John Augustus, as well as framed oil paintings, including "The House I Live in" by Georgia O'Keeffe.
  Boxes 113 and 114 (sound recordings): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 115 (computer disk): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Organized under three headings: Correspondence and Subject Files, Other Papers, and Artwork.
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    Arranged alphabetically either by subject or by correspondent.
    - "A" General, 1939-1990, undated (Box 29)
    - Adams, Frederick B., Jr., 1947-1950
    - Adams, John J., undated
    - Aldington, Richard, 1961
    - Allen, Greer & Sue, 1979-1997
    - American Theatre Museum, 1982-1983
    - Ampersand Books, 1968-1991, undated
    - Anderson, Elizabeth, 1965-1991
    - Anderson, Lee, 1959-1969
    - Anderson, Margaret, 1952-1954, undated
    - Anderson, Sherwood, undated
    - Angus, Ian, 1954-1989
    - Antiquarian Bookman, 1988 July 7
    - Archer, H. Richard, circa 1937-1977
    - Argosy Bookstores, Inc., 1949-1953
    - Atkinson, Brooks, 1971 January 2
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1969-1970
    - Auchincloss, Louis S., 1998
    - Auden, W. H., undated
    - Auerbach, Bart, 1982
    - Ault, Bromwell, 1962-1995
    - "B" General, 1937-2000, undated
    - Babb, James T., 1941-1990, undated
    - Babcock, Bert, 1981-1983
    - Baker, Carlos, 1980
    - Baker, John, 1981-1989
    - Baker, William, 1937-1997
    - Baldwin, Neil, 1984-1988, undated
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1951-1952, undated
    - Banks, Richard, Jr., 1953-1994, undated
    - Banyan Press, 1953-1958, undated
    - Baretti, Giuseppe, 1937-1975, undated
    - Barker, Nicholas, 1968-1989
    - Barnes & Noble, 1992-1998, undated
    - Barrett, Clifton Waller, 1954-1963
    - Bartlett, Ellen, 1934-1936
    - Baskin, Leonard, 1958-1968, undated
    - Beare, Robert L., 1954, undated
    - Beaty, John O., 1929-1942, undated
    - Beauchamp Bookshop, 1952, undated
    - Bell, Book & Radmall, 1975-1976
    - Benét, Thomas Carr, 1949-1998, undated
    - Berlin, Jeffrey B., 1985-1998, undated
    - Bernard, Jules, 1938-1941
    - Bertie, Lady Jean, 1949
    - Bibliographical Society of America, 1947-1999
    - Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia, 1977-2000, undated
    - Bird, William, 1953-1962 (Box 30)
    - Black Sparrow Press, 1967-1978, undated
    - Blanck, Jacob, 1998
    - Blackwell's, 1946-1995, undated
    - Bloomfield, B. C., 1957-1969
    - Bodley Book Shop, 1962-1964
    - Bogard, Travis, 1979-1997, undated; 2
    - Bond, William H., 1998
    - Bonniers, 1946-1952
    - Bontemps, Arna, 1985-1986
    - Book Collector, 1954-1988, undated
    - Book-Of-The-Month Club, 1990-1994
    - Bornstein, George, 1983-1985
    - Boston Athenaeum, 1958-1989, undated
    - Bowers, Fredson, 1981-1991
    - Bowyer, John, 1941; 2
    - Bozyan, Frank, 1978-1991, undated
    - Brainerd, Winthrop, 1961-1999, undated
    - Brennan, Joseph Payne, 1977-1994, undated
    - Brinkley, Margaret & Stuart, 1970-1983, undated
    - Brinnin, John Malcolm, 1981
    - Broadside Press, 1950-1968, undated
    - Brooker, Jewel Spears, 1979-2000, undated; 2
    - Brooker, T. Kim, 1961-1997
    - Brooks, Cleanth, 1960-1994, undated
    - Brooks, John Lee, 1939-1962, undated
    - Browar, Lisa, 1979-2000, undated
    - Brown, Andreas, 1953-1994, undated
    - Brown University, 1962-1999, undated; 3
    - Bruccoli, Matthew J., 1965-1998, undated
    - Brush, Tom & Kitty, 1982-1992 (Box 31)
    - Bry, Doris, 1989-1991
    - Bryer, Jackson R., 1984-1998
    - Burns, Edward, 1972-2000, undated
    - Bush, Ronald, 1978-1984
    - Bywaters, Jerry, 1942-1976
    - "C" General, 1937-1997, undated
    - Cahoon, Herbert, 1949-1987, undated
    - Cannell, Kitty, 1955-1959, undated
    - Cannon, Beekman C., 1961-2000, undated
    - Capsis, John, 1948
    - Cargill, Oscar, 1964-1971
    - Carnegie Book Shop Inc., 1936-1964
    - Carson, Anne, 1999
    - Carter, John, 1948-1976, undated
    - Castro, Jan, 1980-1985, undated
    - Cerf, Bennett, 1952
    - Chamberlain, Elwyn, 1954-1966, undated
    - Charles Rare Books, 1960-1967
    - Chloe's Books, 1988-1990
    - Churchill Club, undated
    - Cincinnati Modern Art Society, 1948-1949
    - City Lights Books, 1990
    - Clark, Frazer, 1973-1978, undated
    - Clark, Hedy, 1961, undated
    - Clodd, H. Alan, 1953-1989, undated
    - Coffin, Catherine, 1970-1977, undated
    - Coffman, Stanley K., Jr., 1947
    - Cohen, Phyllis & Steve, circa 1980-2000; 2
    - Colby College, 1937-1999; 2
    - Columbia University, 1960-1991 (Box 32)
    - Connecticut. Judicial Department, 1990
    - Conroy, Thomas F., 1962-1971, undated
    - Cornell, Julien, 1961
    - Cornell University, 1962-1979
    - Coventry Books, 1991, undated
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1982-1988
    - Cox, Marian, 1964-1971, undated
    - Creekmore, Hubert, 1961-1967
    - Critics' Choice Video, 1996, undated
    - Crook, Arthur, 1968-1973, undated
    - Cross, Robert, circa 1978-1999
    - Csengeri, Karen, 1989, undated
    - Culler, Helen, 1969-1991
    - Curtis, Lewis & Jane, 1956-1992, undated
    - "D" General, 1957-1988, undated
    - Dace, Letitia, 1971-1972
    - Daedalus Books, 1990-1999
    - Dalian Books, 1979-1995
    - Dallas Artists' League, 1937-1938, undated
    - Dallas Museum of Art, 1996-1998
    - Daniels, Earl, 1936-1947
    - Dannenberg, Edgar & Janice, 1963-2000
    - Dantzler, Robert, circa 1961-1999
    - Davies, Jordan, 1982-1986
    - Davis, Dale, 1987-1988
    - Davis, Emy & Fred, 1974-1995; 9
    - Davis, Emy & Fred (continued), 1991-2000; 4 (Box 33)
    - Davison, Peter, 1971-1998